var computerdata = {
  "total_size": 4,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question":
          "Which of these parts would interpret a program’s instructions to initiate the control operations?",
      "option1": "Logic unit",
      "option2": "Control unit",
      "option3": "Storage unit",
      "option4": "Input",
      "ans": "b",
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": " The 1’s complement of 10 is?",
      "option1": "10",
      "option2": "11",
      "option3": "110",
      "option4": "01",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question":
          "__________ is the computer program that would convert an assembly language to the machine language?",
      "option1": "Interpreter",
      "option2": "Compiler",
      "option3": "Comparator",
      "option4": "Assembler",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question":
          "What access method do we use to obtain any record out of a cassette tape?",
      "option1": "Random",
      "option2": "Direct",
      "option3": "Sequential",
      "option4": "All of the above",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "One packet on any data link is called?",
      "option1": "Group",
      "option2": "Block",
      "option3": "Frame",
      "option4": "Path",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question":
          "_____________ is a computer that has been designed so that it is as compact as possible?",
      "option1": "Supercomputer",
      "option2": "Mini",
      "option3": "Mainframe",
      "option4": "Microcomputer",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question":
          "Which of these refers to a systems programming language for the Intel family microcomputers?",
      "option1": "PLA",
      "option2": "PL/CT",
      "option3": "PL/M",
      "option4": "PL/C",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question":
          "What is the number used to control the forms of other numbers known as?",
      "option1": "Mask",
      "option2": "Map",
      "option3": "Marker",
      "option4": "Mantissa",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "A list of various coded instructions is known as?",
      "option1": "Flowchart",
      "option2": "Utility program",
      "option3": "Algorithm",
      "option4": "Computer program",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question":
          "Which of these is a high-level machine-oriented language for the machines that are of the GEC 4080 series?",
      "option1": "ALGOL",
      "option2": "Babbage",
      "option3": "SNOBOL",
      "option4": "LOGO",
      "ans": "b",
    },
  ]
};
